I think I see him!
This way!
- Five.
- Oh, great.
So you got an arrow
right in your chest.
- And you're out 10 melee rounds.
- Oh, no.
Don't worry about it,
Mike. I got resurrection.
I'm already one of the undead.
I can still throw death spells.
I'm just trying to help you out,
man. Don't be so cranky.
How about throwing a
spell over the pizza man?
Where's our pizza, man?
Well, I'm ready now to play.
I'm ready to play now, you guys.
We're in the middle, Elliott. You can't
just join any universe in the middle.
I got him! I got him!
What am I asking for?
- Yeah.
- Mike?
I know. It's not for us,
it's for his mother.
Mike?
- Papa-oom-mow-mow.
- You have to ask Steve. He's game master.
He has absolute power.
- Steve?
- Steve, can I play now?
Go wait for the pizza first.
- Then I'm in?
- Yeah, you're in.
Figure out your strategy.
You're playing after Greg.
Plenty of sausage and pepperonis.
Everything but the little fishies.
Harvey?
Harvey, is that you, boy?
Over here, you guys.
- Stop it.
- Sorry.
Harvey?
All's you can get is
those 40-year-olds.
How do you win this game anyway?
There's no winning. It's like
life. You don't win at life.
Money helps.
- Mom! Mom! There's something out...
- Where's the pizza?
Mom! Mom! There's something
out there! It's in the tool shed.
It threw the ball at me.
Quiet!
Nobody go out there.
Stop. Now, you guys
stay right here.
You stay here, Mom.
We'll check it out.
- And put those knives back!
- Come on, Mom!
It's okay, Elliott.
Let's go get the flashlight.
Hold it. Wait a minute.
Creeps. Creepy.
- What exactly did you see?
- It's dark out here.
In there.
It's scary.
Psst.
There's nothing in here.
The gate's open.
Look at these.
Coyote's come back again, Mom.
Okay, party's over.
Everybody, back inside now.
Get out. Hurry up.
Quick. Hurry up. Come on.
Tyler, give me that knife.
Oh, great. Nice one, Elliott.
It was an accident.
A pizza? Who said you
guys could order a pizza?
Him.
- In the house.
- You geek, man.
- But Mom, it was real. I swear.
- Douche bag.
No douche-bag
talk in my house.
Elliott, you're crazy.
Hello.
Hello?
What are you going
as for Halloween?
I'm not going to stupid Halloween.
Why don't you go as a goblin?
Shut up.
It's not that we don't
believe you, honey.
Well, it was real. I swear.
What are you going as, Gert?
I'm going as a cowgirl.
So what else is new?
- Maybe it was an iguana.
- It was no iguana.
Maybe a...
A...
You know how they say there
are alligators in the sewers?
Alligators in the sewers.
All we're trying to say is, maybe
you just probably imagined it.
I couldn't have imagined it.
Maybe it was a pervert or a
deformed kid or something.
A deformed kid.
Maybe an elf or a leprechaun.
It was nothing like that,
penis breath!
Elliott!
Sit down.
Dad would believe me.
Maybe you ought to call your
father and tell him about it.
I can't. He's in Mexico with Sally.
Where's Mexico?
Excuse me.
I'm going to kill you.
If you ever see it
again, whatever it is,
don't touch it. Just call me.
And we'll have somebody
come and take it away.
Like the dogcatcher?
They'll give it a lobotomy or do
experiments on it or something.
It's your turn to do
the dishes, fellas.
- I set and cleared.
- I did breakfast.
What's the matter, Mom?
He hates Mexico.
Damn it! Why don't you grow up? Think
how other people feel for a change.
Mom.
Mom. Mom!
Michael.
Michael. Mom.
Wow.
Okay, you're hot.
I'll be back.
Mary, can I back the car out?
Not one foot past the driveway.
You were outside last night waiting for
that thing to come back, weren't you?
Are you going to
live if I go to work?
Okay. No TV.
Come on.
Mommy, look what Michael did.
This and that...
I see them, Gert. And when
I catch him, I'll catch him.
Come on. Don't be afraid.
It's all right. Come on.
Come on.
Do you talk?
You know, talk?
Me, human.
Boy.
Elliott.
Coke. See, we drink it.
It's a drink. You know, food?
These are toys.
These are little men.
This is Greedo.
And then, this is Hammerhead.
You see, this is Walrus Man.
And then this is Snaggletooth.
And this is Lando Calrissian. See?
And this is Boba Fett.
Look. They can even
have wars. Look at this.
And look. Fish.
The fish eat the fish food
and the shark eats the fish,
but nobody eats a shark.
See, this is Pez. Candy.
You see, you eat it.
You put the candy in here
and then when you lift up the head, the
candy comes out and you can eat it.
You want some?
This is a peanut.
You eat it.
But you can't eat this one
because this is fake.
This is money. You see?
We put the money in the peanut.
You see? Bank.
You see? And then,
this is a car.
This is what we get around in.
See? A car.
Hey! Hey! Wait a second.
No. You don't eat them.
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry.
Stay.
Stay. I'll be right here.
Okay? I'll be right here.
Harv!
He won't bite.
Come on, Harvey.
He'll like this.
This.
Are you okay?
Too much excitement, huh?
Want a Coke?
There are so many people to see
So many people you can check up
on and add to your collection
But they keep you hanging on
Nothing but health shit.
Add to your collection
But they keep you hanging on
Mike, Mike, come in.
- How you feeling, faker?
- I'm feeling fine.
Look, I got something
really important...
Tyler said he got 69,000
on Asteroids yesterday.
- But he pulled the plug.
- Look, remember the goblin?
You're so lame, Elliott.
Come on, Michael. He came back.
He came back?
Oh, my God!
One thing.
I have absolute power.
Say it. Say it!
What have you got?
Is it the coyote?
No. Look...
Okay. Now, swear it.
The most excellent
promise you can make.
Swear as my only
brother on our lives.
Okay, don't get so heavy. I swear.
Okay. Stand over there.
And uh, you'd better take off...
- ...your shoulder pads.
- What?
You might scare him.
And close your eyes.
Don't push it, Elliott.
I'm not coming out there
until your eyes are closed.
Okay. They're closed.
Mom is going to kill you.
Okay. Swear it one more time.
- I have absolute power.
- You have absolute power.
Yes.
Elliott! Look what I made for you!
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Kids, I'm home!
Guys?
- In the closet, fast.
- Anybody up there, kids?
Anybody home?
Hi, honey, how are you feel...
What happened in here?
Oh, you mean my room.
This is no room.
This is an accident.
I was reorganizing.
I can see that.
Put those shelves back
on the wall, dear.
Let's get the toys off the floor.
Make your bed since
you are not using it.
Well, you're feeling better, I see.
Will you guys keep an eye on Gertie
for me while I take a shower?
Absolutely.
Bye, Mom.
Elliott...
I'm keeping him.
What is it?
He won't hurt you, Gertie.
We're not going to hurt you.
Is he a boy or a girl?
He's a boy.
Was he wearing any clothes?
No.
But, look, you can't tell.
Not even Mom.
Why not?
Because grownups can't see him.
Only little kids can see him.
Give me a break.
Well, do you know
what's going to happen
if you do tell?
Do it, Mike. We have to.
No, please!
No! I'll do anything, please!
Gertie, help me! No, please!
Give it!
- Promise?
- Yes.
Do you promise?
What are you doing, Gert?
I'm going to play
in Elliott's room.
Okay. Don't let him torture you.
I won't, Mary.
Hello?
Jerry! Jerry!
Come on, come on. Hurry up.
Don't be pushy, pushy.
A plant for you.
Maybe he's some animal that
wasn't supposed to live.
You know, like those
rabbits we saw that time.
- Don't be lame.
- Green, orange, red.
Could be a monkey
or an orangutan...
A bald monkey?
Is he a pig? He sure eats like one.
You could make faces.
And make them mean and happy
and make them get sharp teeth.
We are here.
- We're here.
- No, use this.
You could make all sorts of things.
Okay. We're here.
We are here.
Where are you from?
I don't like his feet.
They're only feet,
you little twerp.
He's trying to tell us something.
Earth.
Home.
What's he doing?
What's happening?
Elliott.
Oh, no.
Elliott, what is it?
I don't know. Something scary.
- Got a pulse?
- No, boss.
Hold it. We got it right here.
Follow him.
You think this house?
Did you explain school to him?
How do you explain school
to higher intelligence?
Maybe he's not that smart.
Maybe he's a worker bee
- who only knows how to push buttons.
- He's too smart.
Okay, I just hope we don't
wake up on Mars or something,
surrounded by millions
of little squashy guys.
Hi, Elliott.
- Hey, Elliott, where's your goblin?
- Shut up.
- Did he come back?
- Well, did he?
Yeah, he came back. But he's
not a goblin. He's a spaceman.
As in extraterrestrial.
Where's he from? Uranus?
Get it? Your anus?
- He doesn't get it, Ty.
- Get it? Your anus?
- He doesn't get it.
- You're so immature.
And you're a sine supremus.
- Zero charisma.
- Sine supremus.
Shut up, Greg!
- Zero charisma!
You wimp.
Let's go.
Come on. Get in the car.
We're gonna be late.
Okay, boys and girls, today we will
be doing the actual frog dissection
for which we've been preparing.
And you will find
many similarities.
As you get into the dissection, you
will discover that the anatomy...
The scalpel is very sharp.
Use discretion when
you are cutting.
There will be very little blood.
There may be a few body fluids.
Ugh.
As we get started with
the dissection...
- Ew!
- ...remember that the...
things that you are writing down...
One thing that you should be
looking for during the dissection
is to locate the heart and
notice that it is still beating.
I'm going to once more
emphasize the similarities
of those things which
we see in the...
Similarities with human anatomy...
First of all, here's the heart...
The intestines will be going
through their peristaltic action.
X-W-V-U.
A-F-P.
That is incorrect. The correct
spelling of nuisance is
N-U-I-S-A-N-C-E.
They're pulling us up.
Class, these are the cotton
balls with the chloroform.
And as soon as I get them all in, be
sure and put the lid on right away.
- Ew!
- That's it.
That will start them
going to sleep.
And they won't feel anything.
They won't be hurt.
It'll take a little while.
If you don't want to watch
them, you don't have to.
Say hi.
Can you talk?
Can you say hi?
Hello.
Uncle Ralph!
It's Uncle Ralph, long
distance from California!
I'll talk fast. This call
must be expensive.
No, no, no, no. If I call anytime
on Saturday without an operator,
I can talk for five minutes
for 85 cents plus tax.
If I talk less, I pay less.
Let me talk to that little fella.
Lou, it's Uncle Ralph.
Hello, Uncle Ralph.
Hmm.
Save him.
Run for your life! Back to the
river! Back to the forest!
Run! I want to save you!
Let's get out of here!
Get out!
I got to let him go!
You've got to save him!
Let me handle this!
Class. Let me handle this!
I can handle this.
Let me get this.
Grandpa, what's wrong?
I'm afraid Betsy Sue isn't
going to run tomorrow.
Oh, no. Is it anything serious?
Harvey, I'm home. Come here, boy.
Here he is.
Here's who?
The man from the moon, but I
think you've killed him already.
Honey, just as soon
as I unload the stuff, okay?
Med-bugs.
I want you to meet somebody.
This stuff has gone up
so much in one week.
I want you to meet somebody.
Okay, honey, as soon as I finish
putting all this stuff away, all right?
Oh!
Stupid ragù. I knew it
wouldn't come out.
- "B."
What's with this?
Hello.
Yeah, this is she.
"Basket."
"Bandit."
"Ball."
"Basket. Bandit. Ball."
"Bugs."
"Bananas?
Intoxicated?
You sure you have
the right Elliott?
"B. B."
- "Biscuits."
- B.
But "B" is for boy...
B.
...with a baseball and bat.
You said "B."
B.
You said "B." Good.
Good.
Okay, I'll be right down.
Thank you. Ooh...
Gertie, I have to
go pick up Elliott.
- Will you be a good girl...
- Mommy, he can talk.
Of course he can talk. I'll be right
back in 10 minutes. Stay there.
Ladies and gentlemen, little
Grover here will demonstrate
by chinning himself two times.
- Two times?
- Two times.
- Can I start?
- Okay. Go ahead.
Okay. Here we go.
Phone.
You want to call somebody?
I am not paying for frogs.
Be good. Be good.
Stay here. Stay.
And don't tell anybody. Nobody.
Be good. Be good.
Move.
Oh, God!
- Elliott.
- What?
Elliott.
I taught him how to
talk now. He can talk now.
Elliott!
Look what he brought
up here all by himself.
Elliott.
What's he need this stuff for?
Elliott. Elliott.
E.T. Can you say that?
Can you say E.T.?
E.T.
E.T.  E.T.  E.T.
Be good.
"Be good." I taught him that, too.
You should give him his dignity.
This is the most ridiculous
thing I've ever seen!
Phone.
Phone?
He said "phone"?
Can't you understand
English? He said "phone."
Home.
You're right. That's E.T.'s home.
E.T.
Home, phone.
E.T. phone home.
E.T. phone home. E.T. phone home.
He wants to call somebody.
- What's all this shit?
- E.T. phone home.
Oh, my God, he's talking now.
Home.
E.T. phone home?
E.T. phone home.
And they'll come?
Come.
Home.
- Come on. I promise, Mom.
- What book?
- Any one you want.
- Spiderman...
I'm fine. We'll just put
a smile on our face
and try to get through the evening.
That's all I want to do.
We can't ask Cathy to
go trick-or-treating
in the same old sheet
she wore last year.
Now I wish I would've
listened in science.
Think, Michael.
I guess we should just
grab anything that
looks like he could make
a machine out of.
What would make a radar?
How the hell do I know?
You're the genius here.
You have absolute power, remember?
"I found him. He belongs to me."
You know, Elliott,
- he doesn't look too good anymore.
- Don't say that! We're fine!
What's all this "we" stuff?
You say "we" all the time
now. Really, Elliott...
- ...I think he may be getting sick.
- Look, he's fine.
Okay, okay. Forget I mentioned it.
Grab that Fuzzbuster.
Dad's shirt.
Remember when he used to
take us out to the ball games
and take us to the movies,
and we'd have popcorn fights?
- We'll do that again, Elliott.
- Sure.
Old Spice.
Sea Breeze.
"Peter says, 'The
redskins were defeated?
"'Wendy and the boys
captured by the pirates?
"'I'll rescue her.
I'll rescue her.'
"He leaps, first at his dagger...
"...then at his grindstone
to sharpen it.
"Tink alights near the shell,
and rings out a warning cry.
"'Oh, that is just my medicine.'
"She says, 'Poisoned?
"'Who could've poisoned it?'
"'I promised Wendy to take it and I will,
as soon as I have sharpened my dagger.'
"Tink, who sees its red color
"and remembers the red
of the pirate's eye
"nobly swallows the draft as
Peter's hand is reaching for it.
"'Why, Tink, you have
drunk my medicine.'
"She flutters strangely about the room,
answering him now in a very thin tinkle."
Ouch.
"She says she thinks she
could get well again
"if children believed in fairies.
"Do you believe in fairies?
Say quick that you believe."
I do! I do! I do!
"If you believe, clap your hands.
"Many clap, some don't, a few hiss.
"But Tink is saved. 'Thank you.
"'Oh, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
"'And now to rescue Wendy."'
Can you read it to me again?
"Peter says..."
He's putting it together now.
- I told you he was smart.
- I'm worried, Elliott.
He could blow up the whole house.
He knows what he's doing.
Listen to how he's breathing.
It's going to work.
What's he feeling now?
He's feeling everything.
Now, you're going as
a ghost. You promised.
I'm only pretending I'm
going as a cowgirl.
Okay. Now, you know the
plans by heart, don't you?
Meet you at the lookout.
At the lookout. I'm not
stupid, you know.
Listen, buster. You
won't get four blocks
in this neighborhood
dressed like that.
- Please.
- No, and that is final.
You are not going as a terrorist.
But all the guys are!
I'm not stupid, you know.
Ready?
Ready.
- Wait, Mom. Don't look.
- Okay.
Okay, Mom. You can look now.
Oh, that's great!
Stay here.
Oh...
Ouch.
Stop that! No! Don't!
Ouch. Ouch.
- No. It's a fake knife. It's a fake.
- Ouch. Ouch.
Okay.
All right.
You look great!
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Be back one hour after
sundown. No later.
Ohhh!
Bye.
Gertie, come here. Come on.
Trick or treat?
Home. Home.
Home. Home. Home. Home. Home. Home.
Be back one hour after
sunset. No later.
I'll try as fast as I can, Mike.
You got to cover me.
Well, come on. Help me.
We'll be waiting for you, Elliott.
So come back for sure.
It's too bumpy. We'll
have to walk from here!
E.T.!
Not so high! Not so high!
Ha! Ha!
Don't crash, please.
I really can't believe
you did this.
Your father's going to
hear about this one.
Mexico.
E.T., it's working.
It's working!
Home.
You did it!
It's working!
Home.
E.T., it's working!
Check the door on the left.
We have to go now, E.T.
We're so late already.
We have to go home now, E.T.
You should give them some time.
Ouch.
You could be happy here.
I could take care of you.
I wouldn't let anybody hurt you.
We could grow up together, E.T.
Home.
E.T.?
How was he dressed when last seen?
He was dressed as a
hunchback.
Hunchback.
Is there anything to indicate
that he might have run away?
Any family problems
or recent arguments?
My husband and I just
separated recently
and it hasn't been easy
on the children, but...
My father's in Mexico.
But run away, I...
Where would he have gone?
Elliott.
Oh, Elliott!
Don't ever do this again, Elliott!
Oh, my. You're so hot.
Run up and draw him
a bath. Quick, Gert.
Sorry I yelled at you.
Thanks very much
for all your trouble.
Is he here?
- You've got to find him, Mike.
- Where is he?
In the forest.
At the bald spot.
You've got to find him.
E.T.!
No!
Mom, would you come with me?
What is it?
Mary, just come with me.
Michael, what?
- Mom, remember the goblin?
- Michael, what are you talking about?
Just swear the most excellent
promise you can make.
Michael.
That's terrific.
Mom.
We're sick.
I think we're dying.
- Michael.
- Mom, it's okay.
Downstairs.
He's not going to hurt you, Mom.
He's not gonna hurt you.
Michael, get her downstairs.
It's the man from the moon.
The man from the moon!
You don't know him!
We can't leave him alone.
This is my home!
Home.
The collagen unit, report to
the blue level immediately.
- Does he sleep at night?
- I don't know. I don't know.
What's the matter with Elliott?
Have you noticed any
surface sweating?
No.
- Has it lost any hair?
- He never had any hair.
- Are the children all right?
- Yes.
Did it ever build anything
or write anything down?
Uh... No.
Would you say it has the ability
to manipulate its own environment?
He's smart. He communicates
through Elliott.
Elliott thinks its thoughts.
No. Elliott feels his feelings.
We've identified his primary carrier
protein by electrophoresis.
It's definitely not albumin.
Testing shows no deficit.
Some F&F. HTS test...
EEG analysis shows
complete coherence
and synchronization of brainwave
activity between both subjects.
Skin biopsy reveals
9 millimeters of...
Read isotonic.
Nitrates. 255 million equivalent.
Better do IV and oral contrast.
If there's no response, let's
move to hypertonic saline.
We have meta-starch available.
Cut five per kilo.
CVP line could help.
I think you get more
information with this one gain.
You have no right to do this.
You're scaring him.
You're scaring him!
Respiratory rate, 12.
Good air entry but decreased
tidal volume on the boy.
Put him on O2 five liters by nasal cannula
and draw blood gas in 20 minutes.
Temperature's dropped from
20 to 17 degrees centigrade.
Get a hypothermia blanket...
Please leave him alone.
Can you leave him alone?
I can take care of him.
Get a Doppler-scope in here and
set me up for a 2D cardiac echo.
Skin is cool and diaphoretic.
He's not refusing at all.
He needs inotropic support.
PH is down to 7.03. He's
got metabolic acidosis.
It could be sepsis.
We've drawn two sets
of blood cultures.
He needs broad-spectrum coverage.
How about amp, gen, flagyl?
Elliott.
I've been to the forest.
He shouldn't talk now.
Well, he has to talk now, Major.
Elliott, that machine,
what does it do?
The communicator?
Is it still working?
It's doing something.
What?
I really shouldn't tell.
He came to me.
Elliott, he came to me, too.
I've been wishing for this
since I was 10 years old.
I don't want him to die.
What can we do that
we're not already doing?
He needs to go home.
He's calling his people
and I don't know where they are.
He needs to go home.
Elliott, I don't think that he
was left here intentionally.
But his being here
is a miracle, Elliott.
It's a miracle.
And you did the best
that anybody could do.
I'm glad he met you first.
- He's got DNA.
- Incredible.
- What?
He doesn't have four nucleotides
like we do. He has six.
I've got de-synchronization of
the two brainwave activities.
What are they?
E.T.!
The boy's condition is stabilizing.
His blood pressure's coming back up.
E.T.
Elliott.
- He's speaking.
- He's talking.
E.T., stay with me.
Please.
Stay.
Together.
I'll be right here.
Stay.
Elliott.
The creature's pressure is bottoming out.
His complexes are slow and widening.
How's the boy?
He's converting back to
normal sinus rhythm.
They're separating.
- Yes, definitely separating.
- Boy and creature are separating.
- What does that mean?
- The boy's coming back.
We're losing E.T.
E.T., answer me, please.
- Everything is going to be fine.
- Please.
Just relax.
No!
E.T., don't go!
- No blood pressure.
- He's got no pulse or respiration.
We can't get a pulse or blood
pressure on the creature.
It doesn't look like
he's breathing.
Leave him alone!
You're killing him!
Let's move it!
Get the boy out of
here. Get him away.
Stop it! You're killing him!
You're killing him!
You're killing him! He came to me!
Any pulses? Any pulses?
- Okay, let's go.
- He came to me!
Minimal breath sounds.
Calm down. Calm down. Calm...
Let's try some bretylium. Can
we have some bretylium, please?
Getting a pulse?
Compressed air.
Compressed air's fine.
Thank you.
All IV push.
He's not ventilating.
His pupils are fixed and dilated.
How about some more drugs?
Quiet.
Defibrillate him.
- Everybody, stand clear.
- Clear.
We're losing him.
One more time.
Quiet.
- It's still v-fib.
- Okay, let's go.
Okay. Let's go. Let's go.
Quiet.
Elliott?
Mom.
Try calcium.
He needs some calcium in his body.
Let's continue CPR, please.
Would you people stand back?
Something's happening.
- Ooh, they're going to die.
- Shut up, Greg.
Something is definitely happening.
- Anybody have any ideas?
- EKG's flat.
- Okay, I'm going to call it.
- I think he's dead.
- No. I don't know.
All right. I'm calling it.
What time do you have?
1536.
15 hours, 36 minutes.
Okay.
Let's pack him in ice.
Let's leave.
Is he dead, Mama?
I think so, sweetheart.
Can we wish for him to come back?
Yeah.
I wish.
I wish, too.
Come on, Gert. We'll wait for
Elliott in the front room.
Cardiac arrest was terminated
at 1500 hours and 36 minutes.
He received intravenous lidocaine,
intravenous epinephrine, a lidocaine drip,
2.7% sodium-chloride solution,
catheters from the "A" line.
And the intravenous line
should be sent for culture.
He was monitored with
an EEG and an EKG.
He was defibrillated...
They're going to have
to take him away now.
They're just gonna cut him all up.
Would you like to spend
some time alone with him?
Could we all step out
for a minute, please?
Look at what they've done to you.
I'm so sorry.
You must be dead
because I don't know how to feel.
I can't feel anything anymore.
You've gone someplace else now.
I'll believe in you all my life.
Every day.
E.T.,
I love you.
Oh, my God.
E.T. phone home.
Home. Phone home.
Phone home.
Does this mean they're coming?
Yes.
E.T. phone home. E.T. phone home.
Stay.
Shut up.
Phone.
- Phone home.
- Quiet!
Phone! Phone! Phone!
Would you shut up?
Phone home. E.T. phone home.
E.T. phone home. E.T. phone home.
E.T. phone home.
Phone home.
Phone home. Elliott.
Elliott. Elliott. Elliott.
Elliott?
- Elliott?
- No.
- Elliott, why don't you come with me?
- No. No.
- It's all right.
- No, no.
It'll be all right.
Would you like the flowers?
He's alive! He's alive!
Are they gone, Mama?
- Who's gone, honey?
- The boys.
What boys?
I'm supposed to give you
this note when they're gone.
Give it to me now, Gertie.
Oh, my God.
Give me a hand with this.
- Where's your mask?
- It's back here.
- Well, get it on!
- I'm trying!
Hey, who are you?
I'm driving.
Open the door, son.
There's a guy out here.
What do I do?
What are you waiting for? Let's go!
Well, let's get out
of here, Michael!
I've never driven forward before!
Get the bikes. Meet us at the
playground at the top of the hill.
Let's do it!
Come on, Michael! Go, go, go!
We're all gonna die, and they're
never gonna give me my license.
- Where's the playground?
- It's near the preschool!
- Where's that?
- I don't know streets.
Mom always drives me.
Son of a bitch.
- Where are you going?
- To the spaceship.
- Spaceship?
- To the spaceship to the moon.
Quiet!
Oh, my God.
Stop the van!
Don't pull them off!
That did it!
Okay. He's a man from outer space
and we're taking him to his spaceship.
Well, can't he just beam up?
This is reality, Greg.
- Keep her back!
- No!
- Hold her back!
- No guns! They're children!
No! No! No!
- Where are they?
- No!
There's nobody here.
Where are we going?
To the forest!
Follow me!
We got them, at the
bottom of the hill.
This is Unit 302.
We've cut the kids off at the bottom
of the hill. Send backup units.
Let's split up.
Okay!
Hang on!
We made it! Oh, shit!
- Whoa!
Tell me when it's over!
Ah.
Home.
Stop the car, Mama!
They're over there!
I just wanted to say goodbye.
He doesn't know goodbye.
Be good.
Yes.
Ah.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Come.
Stay.
Ouch.
I'll be right here.
Bye.